# NIC STEEL

I.T. ADMINISTRATOR

I am a seasoned IT professional with over 7 years of experience. My goal at this point in my career is to capitalize upon new opportunities for career development within an organization that values hard work, integrity, and results. I look forward to hearing if I am a good fit for the IT Technician position.

# CONTACT INFORMATION

- 641-670-1237
- nicholasssteel@gmail.com
- in linkedin.com/in/nicholasssteel

# EDUCATION BACKGROUND

#### **William Penn University**

BACHELOR'S OF FINE ARTS

## **SKILLS**

PROBLEM SOLVING

EXCELLENT COMMUNICATION

TIME MANAGEMENT

LEARNS QUICKLY

CONSISTENT FOLLOW THROUGH

CUSTOMER SERVICE EXPERIENCE

LISTENS AND ADAPTS TO FFEDBACK



SPECIALIZATIONS

- Project Management
- Desktop and Network Support
- Asset Management
- •Tech Solutions

## WORK EXPERIENCE

#### **IT Administrator**

CUNNINGHAM INC
OCT 2019 TO PRESENT

- Improved company workflow by 43% by reorganizing folders
- Implemented ticketing system to reduce company downtime
- Key Achievement Solved network problems that prevented employees from working remotely due to COVID-19 pandemic

## PC Technician - Contract

PRINCIPAL FINANCIAL GROUP JUN 2019 TO OCT 2019

- Streamlined the on-boarding process by imaging and patching large groups of laptops prior to people being hired.
- Key Achievement Coordinated multi-floor upgrades to keep downtime to a minimum while increasing workflow by 30%

#### **Network Support Specialist - Contract**

MANATTS INC SEP 2018 TO JUN 2019

- Collaborated with cross-functional project teams of 15 colleagues from Fleet and Field departments to provide tailor-made support for the end users.
- *Key Achievement* Negotiated with cellular providers on cell plans, saving the company \$60,000 annually.

#### **Information Technology Librarian**

WILLIAM PENN UNIVERSITY AUG 2013 TO SEP 2018

- Trained and mentored 5+ student workers a year to offer library and technical support.
- Key Achievement Archived and documented 10+ photos daily to be preserved on our online database, reducing the need for physical storage.